[
{"Front": "間", "Back": "あいだ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "合う", "Back": "あう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "上る", "Back": "あがる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "赤ん坊", "Back": "あかんぼう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "空く", "Back": "あく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "浅い", "Back": "あさい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "味", "Back": "あじ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "明日", "Back": "あす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "遊び", "Back": "あそび", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "集る", "Back": "あつまる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "集める", "Back": "あつめる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "謝る", "Back": "あやまる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "安心", "Back": "あんしん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "安全", "Back": "あんぜん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "案内", "Back": "あんない・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "以下", "Back": "いか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "以外", "Back": "いがい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "医学", "Back": "いがく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "生きる", "Back": "いきる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "意見", "Back": "いけん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "石", "Back": "いし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "以上", "Back": "いじょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "急ぐ", "Back": "いそぐ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "致す", "Back": "いたす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "一度", "Back": "いちど", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "一生懸命", "Back": "いっしょうけんめい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "糸", "Back": "いと", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "以内", "Back": "いない", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "田舎", "Back": "いなか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "祈る", "Back": "いのる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "植える", "Back": "うえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "受付", "Back": "うけつけ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "受ける", "Back": "うける", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "動く", "Back": "うごく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "打つ", "Back": "うつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "美しい", "Back": "うつくしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "写す", "Back": "うつす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "移る", "Back": "うつる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "腕", "Back": "うで", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "裏", "Back": "うら", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "売り場", "Back": "うりば", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "運転", "Back": "うんてん・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "運転手", "Back": "うんてんしゅ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "運動", "Back": "うんどう・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "枝", "Back": "えだ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "選ぶ", "Back": "えらぶ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "遠慮", "Back": "えんりょ・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お祝い", "Back": "おいわい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "億", "Back": "おく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "屋上", "Back": "おくじょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "贈り物", "Back": "おくりもの", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "送る", "Back": "おくる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "遅れる", "Back": "おくれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "起す", "Back": "おこす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "行う", "Back": "おこなう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "怒る", "Back": "おこる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "押し入れ", "Back": "おしいれ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お嬢さん", "Back": "おじょうさん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お宅", "Back": "おたく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "落る", "Back": "おちる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "夫", "Back": "おっと", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "音", "Back": "おと", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "落す", "Back": "おとす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "踊り", "Back": "おどり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "踊る", "Back": "おどる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "驚く", "Back": "おどろく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お祭り", "Back": "おまつり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お見舞い", "Back": "おみまい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お土産", "Back": "おみやげ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "思い出す", "Back": "おもいだす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "思う", "Back": "おもう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "表", "Back": "おもて", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "親", "Back": "おや", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "下りる", "Back": "おりる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "折る", "Back": "おる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お礼", "Back": "おれい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "折れる", "Back": "おれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "終わり", "Back": "おわり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "海岸", "Back": "かいがん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "会議", "Back": "かいぎ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "会議室", "Back": "かいぎしつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "会場", "Back": "かいじょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "会話", "Back": "かいわ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "帰り", "Back": "かえり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "変える", "Back": "かえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "科学", "Back": "かがく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "鏡", "Back": "かがみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "掛ける", "Back": "かける", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "飾る", "Back": "かざる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "火事", "Back": "かじ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "堅/硬/固い", "Back": "かたい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "形", "Back": "かたち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "片付ける", "Back": "かたづける", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "課長", "Back": "かちょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "勝つ", "Back": "かつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "家内", "Back": "かない", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "悲しい", "Back": "かなしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "必ず", "Back": "かならず", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "お・金持ち", "Back": "かねもち/おかねもち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "彼女", "Back": "かのじょ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "壁", "Back": "かべ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "髪", "Back": "かみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "噛む", "Back": "かむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "通う", "Back": "かよう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "彼", "Back": "かれ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "彼ら", "Back": "かれら", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "乾く", "Back": "かわく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "代わり", "Back": "かわり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "変わる", "Back": "かわる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "考える", "Back": "かんがえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "関係", "Back": "かんけい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "看護婦", "Back": "かんごふ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "簡単", "Back": "かんたん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "気", "Back": "き", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "機会", "Back": "きかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "危険", "Back": "きけん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "聞こえる", "Back": "きこえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "汽車", "Back": "きしゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "技術", "Back": "ぎじゅつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "季節", "Back": "きせつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "規則", "Back": "きそく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "絹", "Back": "きぬ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "厳しい", "Back": "きびしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "気分", "Back": "きぶん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "決る", "Back": "きまる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "君", "Back": "きみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "決める", "Back": "きめる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "気持ち", "Back": "きもち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "着物", "Back": "きもの", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "客", "Back": "きゃく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "急", "Back": "きゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "急行", "Back": "きゅうこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "教育", "Back": "きょういく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "教会", "Back": "きょうかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "競争", "Back": "きょうそう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "興味", "Back": "きょうみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "近所", "Back": "きんじょ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "具合", "Back": "ぐあい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "空気", "Back": "くうき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "空港", "Back": "くうこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "草", "Back": "くさ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "首", "Back": "くび", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "雲", "Back": "くも", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "比べる", "Back": "くらべる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "暮れる", "Back": "くれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "毛", "Back": "け", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "計画", "Back": "けいかく・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "経験", "Back": "けいけん・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "経済", "Back": "けいざい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "警察", "Back": "けいさつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "景色", "Back": "けしき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "消しゴム", "Back": "けしゴム", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "下宿", "Back": "げしゅく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "決して", "Back": "けっして", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "原因", "Back": "げんいん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "研究", "Back": "けんきゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "研究室", "Back": "けんきゅうしつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "見物", "Back": "けんぶつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "子", "Back": "こ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "郊外", "Back": "こうがい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "講義", "Back": "こうぎ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "工業", "Back": "こうぎょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "高校", "Back": "こうこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "高校生", "Back": "こうこうせい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "工場", "Back": "こうじょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "校長", "Back": "こうちょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "交通", "Back": "こうつう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "講堂", "Back": "こうどう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "高等学校", "Back": "こうとうがっこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "公務員", "Back": "こうむいん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "国際", "Back": "こくさい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "心", "Back": "こころ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "御主人", "Back": "ごしゅじん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "故障", "Back": "こしょう・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "ご存じ", "Back": "ごぞんじ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "答", "Back": "こたえ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "小鳥", "Back": "ことり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "細かい", "Back": "こまかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "込む", "Back": "こむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "米", "Back": "こめ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "怖い", "Back": "こわい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "壊す", "Back": "こわす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "壊れる", "Back": "こわれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "今度", "Back": "こんど", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "今夜", "Back": "こんや", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "最近", "Back": "さいきん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "最後", "Back": "さいご", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "最初", "Back": "さいしょ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "坂", "Back": "さか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "探す", "Back": "さがす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "下る", "Back": "さがる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "盛ん", "Back": "さかん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "下げる", "Back": "さげる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "差し上げる", "Back": "さしあげる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "寂しい", "Back": "さびしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "さ来月", "Back": "さらいげつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "さ来週", "Back": "さらいしゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "騒ぐ", "Back": "さわぐ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "触る", "Back": "さわる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "産業", "Back": "さんぎょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "残念", "Back": "ざんねん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "市", "Back": "し", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "字", "Back": "じ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "試合", "Back": "しあい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "仕方", "Back": "しかた", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "試験", "Back": "しけん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "事故", "Back": "じこ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "地震", "Back": "じしん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "時代", "Back": "じだい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "下着", "Back": "したぎ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "支度", "Back": "したく・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "失敗", "Back": "しっぱい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "辞典", "Back": "じてん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "品物", "Back": "しなもの", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "島", "Back": "しま", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "市民", "Back": "しみん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "事務所", "Back": "じむしょ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "社会", "Back": "しゃかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "社長", "Back": "しゃちょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "自由", "Back": "じゆう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "習慣", "Back": "しゅうかん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "住所", "Back": "じゅうしょ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "柔道", "Back": "じゅうどう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "十分", "Back": "じゅうぶん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "出席", "Back": "しゅっせき・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "出発", "Back": "しゅっぱつ・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "趣味", "Back": "しゅみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "準備", "Back": "じゅんび・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "紹介", "Back": "しょうかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "小学校", "Back": "しょうがっこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "小説", "Back": "しょうせつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "招待", "Back": "しょうたい・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "承知", "Back": "しょうち・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "将来", "Back": "しょうらい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "食事", "Back": "しょくじ・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "食料品", "Back": "しょくりょうひん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "女性", "Back": "じょせい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "知らせる", "Back": "しらせる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "調べる", "Back": "しらべる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "人口", "Back": "じんこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "神社", "Back": "じんじゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "親切", "Back": "しんせつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "心配", "Back": "しんぱい・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "新聞社", "Back": "しんぶんしゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "水泳", "Back": "すいえい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "水道", "Back": "すいどう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "数学", "Back": "すうがく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "過ぎる", "Back": "すぎる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "凄い", "Back": "すごい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "進む", "Back": "すすむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "捨てる", "Back": "すてる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "砂", "Back": "すな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "滑る", "Back": "すべる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "隅", "Back": "すみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "済む", "Back": "すむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "生活", "Back": "せいかつ・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "生産", "Back": "せいさん・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "政治", "Back": "せいじ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "西洋", "Back": "せいよう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "世界", "Back": "せかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "席", "Back": "せき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "説明", "Back": "せつめい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "背中", "Back": "せなか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "世話", "Back": "せわ・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "線", "Back": "せん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "戦争", "Back": "せんそう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "先輩", "Back": "せんぱい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "相談", "Back": "そうだん・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "育てる", "Back": "そだてる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "卒業", "Back": "そつぎょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "祖父", "Back": "そふ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "祖母", "Back": "そぼ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "退院", "Back": "たいいん・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大学生", "Back": "だいがくせい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大事", "Back": "だいじ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大体", "Back": "だいたい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "大分", "Back": "だいぶ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "台風", "Back": "たいふう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "倒れる", "Back": "たおれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "確か", "Back": "たしか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "足す", "Back": "たす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "訪ねる", "Back": "たずねる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "尋ねる", "Back": "たずねる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "正しい", "Back": "ただしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "畳", "Back": "たたみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "立てる", "Back": "たてる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "建てる", "Back": "たてる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "例えば", "Back": "たとえば", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "棚", "Back": "たな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "楽しみ", "Back": "たのしみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "楽む", "Back": "たのしむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "為", "Back": "ため", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "足りる", "Back": "たりる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "男性", "Back": "だんせい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "暖房", "Back": "だんぼう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "血", "Back": "ち", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "力", "Back": "ちから", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "注意", "Back": "ちゅうい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "中学校", "Back": "ちゅうがっこう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "注射", "Back": "ちゅうしゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "駐車場", "Back": "ちゅうしゃじょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "地理", "Back": "ちり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "捕まえる", "Back": "つかまえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "付く", "Back": "つく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "漬ける", "Back": "つける", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "都合", "Back": "つごう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "伝える", "Back": "つたえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "続く", "Back": "つづく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "続ける", "Back": "つづける", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "包む", "Back": "つつむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "妻", "Back": "つま", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "釣る", "Back": "つる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "連れる", "Back": "つれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "丁寧", "Back": "ていねい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "適当", "Back": "てきとう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "手伝う", "Back": "てつだう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "手袋", "Back": "てぶくろ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "寺", "Back": "てら", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "点", "Back": "てん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "店員", "Back": "てんいん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "天気予報", "Back": "てんきよほう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "電灯", "Back": "でんとう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "電報", "Back": "でんぽう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "展覧会", "Back": "てんらんかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "都", "Back": "と", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "道具", "Back": "どうぐ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "動物園", "Back": "どうぶつえん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "遠く", "Back": "とおく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "通る", "Back": "とおる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "特に", "Back": "とくに", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "特別", "Back": "とくべつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "途中", "Back": "とちゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "特急", "Back": "とっきゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "届ける", "Back": "とどける", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "泊まる", "Back": "とまる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "止める", "Back": "とめる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "取り替える", "Back": "とりかえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "泥棒", "Back": "どろぼう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "直す", "Back": "なおす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "直る", "Back": "なおる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "治る", "Back": "なおる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "中々", "Back": "なかなか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "泣く", "Back": "なく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "無くなる", "Back": "なくなる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "投げる", "Back": "なげる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "亡くなる", "Back": "なくなる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "鳴る", "Back": "なる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "慣れる", "Back": "なれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "苦い", "Back": "にがい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "二階建て", "Back": "にかいだて", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "逃げる", "Back": "にげる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "日記", "Back": "にっき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "入院", "Back": "にゅういん・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "入学", "Back": "にゅうがく・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "似る", "Back": "にる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "盗む", "Back": "ぬすむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "人形", "Back": "にんぎょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "塗る", "Back": "ぬる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "熱", "Back": "ねつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "寝坊", "Back": "ねぼう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "眠い", "Back": "ねむい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "眠る", "Back": "ねむる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "残る", "Back": "のこる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "乗り換える", "Back": "のりかえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "乗り物", "Back": "のりもの", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "葉", "Back": "は", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "場合", "Back": "ばあい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "倍", "Back": "ばい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "拝見", "Back": "はいけん・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "歯医者", "Back": "はいしゃ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "運ぶ", "Back": "はこぶ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "始める", "Back": "はじめる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "場所", "Back": "ばしょ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "恥ずかしい", "Back": "はずかしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "発音", "Back": "はつおん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "花見", "Back": "はなみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "林", "Back": "はやし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "払う", "Back": "はらう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "番組", "Back": "ばんぐみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "反対", "Back": "はんたい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "日", "Back": "ひ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "火", "Back": "ひ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "冷える", "Back": "ひえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "光", "Back": "ひかり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "光る", "Back": "ひかる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "引き出し", "Back": "ひきだし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "引き出す", "Back": "ひきだす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "飛行場", "Back": "ひこうじょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "久しぶり", "Back": "ひさしぶり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "美術館", "Back": "びじゅつかん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "非常に", "Back": "ひじょうに", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "引っ越す", "Back": "ひっこす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "必要", "Back": "ひつよう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "開く", "Back": "ひらく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "昼間", "Back": "ひるま", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "昼休み", "Back": "ひるやすみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "拾う", "Back": "ひろう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "増える", "Back": "ふえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "深い", "Back": "ふかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "複雑", "Back": "ふくざつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "復習", "Back": "ふくしゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "部長", "Back": "ぶちょう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "普通", "Back": "ふつう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "太る", "Back": "ふとる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "布団", "Back": "ふとん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "舟", "Back": "ふね", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "不便", "Back": "ふべん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "踏む", "Back": "ふむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "降り出す", "Back": "ふりだす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "文化", "Back": "ぶんか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "文学", "Back": "ぶんがく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "文法", "Back": "ぶんぽう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "別", "Back": "べつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "変", "Back": "へん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "返事", "Back": "へんじ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "貿易", "Back": "ぼうえき", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "放送", "Back": "ほうそう・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "法律", "Back": "ほうりつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "僕", "Back": "ぼく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "星", "Back": "ほし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "翻訳", "Back": "ほんやく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "参る", "Back": "まいる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "負ける", "Back": "まける", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "間違える", "Back": "まちがえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "間に合う", "Back": "まにあう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "周り", "Back": "まわり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "回る", "Back": "まわる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "漫画", "Back": "まんが", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "真中", "Back": "まんなか", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "見える", "Back": "みえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "湖", "Back": "みずうみ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "味噌", "Back": "みそ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "見つかる", "Back": "みつかる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "見つける", "Back": "みつける", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "皆", "Back": "みな", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "港", "Back": "みなと", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "向かう", "Back": "むかう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "迎える", "Back": "むかえる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "昔", "Back": "むかし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "虫", "Back": "むし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "息子", "Back": "むすこ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "娘", "Back": "むすめ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "無理", "Back": "むり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "召し上がる", "Back": "めしあがる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "珍しい", "Back": "めずらしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "申し上げる", "Back": "もうしあげる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "申す", "Back": "もうす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "戻る", "Back": "もどる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "木綿", "Back": "もめん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "森", "Back": "もり", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "焼く", "Back": "やく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "約束", "Back": "やくそく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "役に立つ", "Back": "やくにたつ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "焼ける", "Back": "やける", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "優しい", "Back": "やさしい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "痩せる", "Back": "やせる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "止む", "Back": "やむ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "柔らかい", "Back": "やわらかい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "湯", "Back": "ゆ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "輸出", "Back": "ゆしゅつ・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "輸入", "Back": "ゆにゅう・する", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "指", "Back": "ゆび", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "指輪", "Back": "ゆびわ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "夢", "Back": "ゆめ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "揺れる", "Back": "ゆれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "用", "Back": "よう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "用意", "Back": "ようい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "用事", "Back": "ようじ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "汚れる", "Back": "よごれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "予習", "Back": "よしゅう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "予定", "Back": "よてい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "予約", "Back": "よやく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "寄る", "Back": "よる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "喜ぶ", "Back": "よろこぶ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "理由", "Back": "りゆう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "利用", "Back": "りよう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "両方", "Back": "りょうほう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "旅館", "Back": "りょかん", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "留守", "Back": "るす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "冷房", "Back": "れいぼう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "歴史", "Back": "れきし", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "連絡", "Back": "れんらく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "沸かす", "Back": "わかす", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "別れる", "Back": "わかれる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "沸く", "Back": "わく", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "訳", "Back": "わけ", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "忘れ物", "Back": "わすれもの", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "笑う", "Back": "わらう", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "割合", "Back": "わりあい", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "割れる", "Back": "われる", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"},
{"Front": "泳ぎ方", "Back": "およぎかた", "Tags": [], "Deck": "n4-vocab-kanji-hiragana"}
]